{
  "moduleCode": "M-11-11-11",
  "title": "con cac",
  "description": "<p>HIHIHIHIHIHI</p>",
  "difficulty": "Beginner",
  "duration": 30,
  "content": "<p>HIHIHIHIHIHIHIHIHI</p>",
  "caseStudy": [
    {
      "title": "case 1",
      "content": "HIHIHIHI",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "ok",
          "answer": "awda"
        },
        {
          "question": "HI",
          "answer": "HI"
        },
        {
          "question": "ok",
          "answer": "awdaHI"
        },
        {
          "question": "HIHI",
          "answer": "HIHIHIHIHIHIHI"
        },
        {
          "question": "test",
          "answer": "asdsaddsadsa"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "test case study 2",
      "content": "dasdasd",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "sadsad",
          "answer": "asda"
        },
        {
          "question": "sadsad",
          "answer": "asdsadas"
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "quiz": [
    {
      "question": "adda",
      "options": [
        "adad",
        "daad",
        "adad",
        "adadaaaa"
      ],
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "question": "HI",
      "options": [
        "HI",
        "HIHI",
        "HIHIHIHI",
        "HIHIHIHIHI"
      ],
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "question": "henry",
      "options": [
        "henry",
        "dasdsa",
        "dsadsad",
        "sadasd"
      ],
      "correct": "A"
    }
  ],
  "createdAt": "2025-02-20T21:48:12.671Z",
  "hasCaseStudy": true,
  "hasQuiz": true,
  "updatedAt": "2025-02-24T13:16:51.826Z"
}